(Leonard:)Penny kissing me is not insane.
(Leonard:)She used to kiss me
all the time.
(Sheldon:)Einstein defined insanity
as "doing the same thing
(Sheldon:)over and over again and
expecting different results."
(Sheldon:)By that standard,
(Sheldon:)Penny is cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
(Leonard:)I'm just saying,
(Leonard:)it felt like it may have
meant something.
(Howard:)Ah, this takes me back.
(Howard:)Leonard obsessing about Penny.
(Howard:)I mean, don't get me wrong,
I love your new stuff,
(Howard:)but once in a while
it's nice to hear the hits.
(Raj:)Ooh, ooh!
Do "Our babies will be smart
and beautiful."
(Raj:)That one always makes me laugh.
(Leonard:)Why do I bother
talking to you people?
(Sheldon:)If it'll make you feel better,
we rarely listen.
(Penny(at door):)Hey, can I talk to you
out here for a sec?
(Leonard:)Yeah, sure.
(Sheldon:)I'm starting to think we're
never going to see that pizza.
(Penny:)So you're probably wondering
what that was all about.
(Leonard:)What, uh, the kissing
and everything?
(Leonard:)Nah, women do that to me
all the time.